[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
One seven two nine
Five seven two two
Two one three three
One nine five zero
Three two five three
Jinlan.
You're here early too.
Perfect timing, I need to talk to you.
Yesterday, I was just a step too late.
If I had come back five minutes earlier,
I could have caught you.
Actually, it's no big deal.
It was just a file cover.
But file covers need to be locked up too.
The higher-ups don't care
whether it holds top secrets or toilet paper.
Never,
ever groundlessly suspect
your own comrades and brothers-in-arms.
Unless
you can produce ironclad evidence.
I'm not mad.
I'm just here to make a profit.
Even a sow needs to be fattened up before slaughter.
Asking me for ten thousand right off the bat...
Do they take me for a fool?
Brother, if you handle the takeoff, you gotta handle the landing.
You can't lure me here to invest and leave me to fend for myself.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Absolutely not.
That's not what I meant.
A fine is definitely in order,
but please don't make it so steep.
I'm just a nobody.
I can't afford to offend anyone.
Just reduce the fine a little.
Anyway, you host the dinner, I'll foot the bill.
Premium Kaoliang.
It's set for tonight.
Where's your pushy classmate?
She'll be half an hour late.
I'm the one who notified her.
This story is off to an interesting start.
Have a seat.
She quoted you 20 a person.
You doubled it to 40.
But she only gave us 30 each.
You can come to me for any future events.
I'll find the people for you.
There are plenty of volunteers.
We only ask for 35.
We can go even lower.
I need to head back.
There won't be a next time.
With you being so aggressive,
who would ever hire you again?
People need to trust each other.
This partnership wasn't pleasant.
Let's not talk business anymore.
Last time was an accident.
Taking your watch was...
But on a personal level,
we're still friends.
Open it and take a look.
If you like it,
I can give it to you.
Let me put it on for you.
Turn around.
It suits you.
Can I just not tell Jin Li'na?
That's up to you.
Boss Lin.
Elder Lin.
You're here.
Professor Cao, Deputy Chief Engineer.
Congratulations, Professor Cao.
Congratulations on your promotion to Deputy Chief Engineer.
Congratulations.
You count it too.
No need.
Boss Lin wouldn't cheat us.
If he meant to,
he wouldn't have called us.
The shoes.
And the sneakers.
Just like we agreed.
Right here.
You already gave them to me before you came in.
Why are there only two pairs?
What about the others?
I only promised to give them to you two.
Give one to everybody?
Am I crazy?
But that's not what you said before.
Jin Lina.
That's enough.
How am I supposed to explain this to them?
Just give them the money.
Maybe they forgot about it.
You can call the police.
You can call the cops over.
Let them be the judge.
From now on, good or bad,
put it all in the contract.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Why are you looking at me?
This isn't my watch.
How can it not be your watch?
This is your watch.
This is a fake.
Now it's my turn to call the police.
Lu Zhifei! Lu Zhifei!
I just went to Pacific.
You weren't on comp time.
You took personal leave.
I also went to the place you rented.
Who was that waiting for you at the door?
He didn't look like a good guy.
Xiao Jiang has already gone back home.
Why did you guys lie to me?
What are you hiding from?
I'm not hiding from anything!
You're still lying to me.
Then let me ask you.
Where's the watch?
Do you have any idea how much that watch is worth?
A hundred thousand yuan!
Now they want to press charges for theft.
You'll spend at least twenty years in prison.
You'll rot in there, you idiot!
Some look like dates.
Others, I can't figure out.
Where did you get this?
From an old cold case.
Notes taken by a suspect.
It is hard to guess.
That's why it's a cold case.
There's no logic to it.
I can't analyze it.
What about the Provincial Department?
Do they have any other way?
There's no context,
and no correlation.
It makes absolutely no sense.
No one can do anything about it.
Chunxiao.
No wonder I didn't see you just now.
You came to Xiaowu to get something analyzed?
Chief Wei said to go over all the Taiwan Strait cold cases.
There's too much stuff to analyze.
Where are you going?
My car keeps breaking down.
It has too many minor issues.
I'm going to the maintenance team.
Your car still isn't fixed?
Didn't they say they couldn't find the problem?
That's just how I am.
The harder it is to find the problem,
the more I want to figure out what's wrong with it.
True.
It'll be easier to commute once it's fixed.
I heard you rent your place.
I don't want to live at home anymore either.
My mom nags too much.
Did you find it yourself?
I asked door to door.
You can also ask the Neighborhood Committee.
It's more convenient.
Which street do you live on?
Is it easy to get around?
What do you mean by a pawn agency?
Isn't it just a pawnshop?
Which one?
Not far from the station.
The first one at the entrance of Dongxi Alley.
How much did they charge you?
The maximum renewal period is one month.
Plus an eight percent service fee.
And after a month?
How will you pay it back?
Plus another 0.5 percent.
The sky isn't falling.
At worst, we borrow and pay it back together.
That would have worked.
Did you have to scam people with a fake watch?
Don't you know if you dare to commit fraud now,
you'll dare to kill tomorrow?
Are the people who made you take photos forcing you?
Are you really hiding from creditors?
Say something!
No, it's not like that.
It's the photo studio boss.
I broke his Canon camera before.
And the camera got confiscated too.
I can't drag my friend down with me.
What do you mean by dragging your friend down?
Was the money you got from pawning not enough?
No, it wasn't.
I have to help Xiaojiang cover his debts.
I borrowed from a loan shark.
Auntie,
well,
I want to discuss something with you.
Lina,
you don't have to agree.
A classmate at our school got sick.
So the school is organizing a loan.
Right.
It's a loan, not a donation.
They just want everyone to help out.
And that classmate is in my dorm.
Alright.
Bye-bye.
Mr. Zhang, can I make another call?
Go ahead, go ahead.
This is Jin Lina.
I just want to see you.
Are you free?
Maybe tonight?
I want to borrow some money
to get your watch back first.
I can write an IOU.
I can leave my fingerprint.
I'll pay it back slowly.
I can even pay interest.
If you need volunteers again in the future,
I'll help you find people.
I won't take any money myself.
I'll leave my student ID with you.
You know where my school is.
I can't run away.
Where is your home?
My hometown is in Sichuan.
I have relatives here too.
My aunt's house is right
in the military compound next to the weather station.
The military, huh?
There are soldiers at the gate.
Holding guns.
If you hide inside,
how am I supposed to get in?
Then I'll agree to whatever you want.
You use my money
to buy back my watch,
and expect me to owe you a favor.
And you tell me to find a way out.
But I haven't even said
if I'll call the cops on your boyfriend
and have him sentenced.
He's just an idiot.
He foolishly got mixed up with the wrong crowd.
He was supposed to come with me today
to apologize to you.
But right before we left, he chickened out.
Actually, all of this is my fault.
Even if you beat me to death,
I had no idea this watch was so expensive.
If I had known,
Stand up.
Turn around and let me see.
What do you want?
A work-study job.
Have you considered it?
You're too thin.
And you don't wear makeup.
But you have a decent foundation.
If you clean up a bit,
you'll be presentable enough to take out.
I'll hire you as my secretary.
You don't have to work every day.
When I need you,
just take time off from school.
Your salary will be paid monthly,
with a year-end bonus.
How does that sound?
What do you mean?
I'll redeem the watch myself.
Consider the money a loan for now.
Pay me back when you've saved up your wages.
It's better than not getting my old debt back,
and having to give you even more money.
Okay.
But can I...
get a month's salary in advance?
Are you always this shameless?
Xiao Lu still has to pay for the camera.
His friend owes loan sharks and needs cash fast.
Why didn't you ask how much your salary is?
No matter how much it is,
I couldn't ask for a two-month advance.
I wouldn't have the nerve.
I find you quite interesting.
Then, as your secretary,
what will I be doing?
First, a trip to Beijing.
To discuss some business.
When?
Wait for my word.
Maybe tomorrow.
Maybe the day after.
Eat up. It's quite good.
How is it?
Delicious.
The car's gone.
Why are you still taking pictures?
Let's go. Time to go home.
Why won't it start again?
Wasn't it just fixed earlier today?
The maintenance crew can never fix it right.
How about this?
I'll drive it to the repair shop in a bit.
I just don't know what time they get off work.
Might as well let it break completely.
Once it gets to the point where it can't be fixed,
there'll be no need to fix it anymore.
What do you mean?
By the way, Uncle,
Second Grandpa said
those of us who have regular jobs
don't need to go back this time.
Wait until the ancestral hall is fully renovated,
we'll pick a date,
and then go back together.
Originally, they wanted you to host it,
but I said you had to go to Beijing to meet the leaders.
It's a matter of bringing honor to our ancestors.
Our ancestors will understand.
Just take whatever money is needed from the cabinet.
Wait a while,
and you can take it down to the countryside.
Okay.
Step aside.
Let me do it.
Uncle,
this time, is Mayor Xie
going with you?
It's not government business.
Why would he go?
I... I was thinking,
look,
I've been at the Sports Bureau for so many years.
Always jumping around there,
it's not very interesting.
I want to transfer
to a better department.
I just draw blueprints and do math.
These things...
I'm afraid I really can't say them.
Aren't you about to be promoted to Deputy Chief Engineer?
When you come back from Beijing,
the leaders will definitely meet you.
If you get close to them,
it just takes a single word.
You should first get your professional title
sorted out.
How many times have I told you?
You just won't listen to me.
If the leaders really ask about it,
won't they still ask about your own qualifications?
I don't think the others have such great qualifications.
Uncle, you need to speak up about this.
Anyway, I think Aunt is right.
You can't be too shy.
If you don't tell anyone,
no one will offer to help you.
Just like this time with your housing allocation,
you have to speak up.
Not only do you have to speak up,
you should also visit the leaders' homes.
That's completely unnecessary.
How can a Deputy Chief Engineer not have an apartment?
Use common sense.
It's just like Zhuge Liang
not believing Sima Yi would enter the city.
Why put on a show if you aren't confident?
That's just an opera.
I just don't believe Sima Yi wouldn't dare enter the city.
Would he dare?
It's a deadly trap where you'll lose your head.
Director.
I'm off the clock, Section Chief Wei.
You're late.
If it's business, it can wait until tomorrow.
Don't bother if it's trivial.
I have important business with you.
When is it ever not important with you?
Let's go. Come on.
Let's go inside. It's classified.
I'm here to "bribe" you.
Your "bribe", huh?
It better be good.
Guaranteed to satisfy.
Today is my mother-in-law's birthday.
If it were my own mother's birthday,
being late wouldn't be a big deal.
Requesting a replacement vehicle.
Section 2's Santana is broken.
The engine is leaking.
Alright.
Get in line.
I have a reason to cut the line.
Recruitment attempts have noticeably increased lately.
The methods are endless.
There's a relative of a military officer.
This girl is a student at the teachers' college.
Her aunt,
although not high in rank,
holds a very crucial position and status.
Her uncle works near the military compound,
at a local hospital.
Although he has no military status,
he can easily
come into contact with military personnel.
This guy is a Taiwanese businessman.
On the day the "Postman" was arrested,
he was seen at the crime scene.
Also, rumor has it
that he'll be leaving Minzhong soon.
If he's heading to Beijing,
just like the guest coming from Taipei,
then things get interesting.
Lin Kanshan.
Right.
Seeing a mountain as a mountain,
seeing a mountain as not a mountain.
Interesting.
Requesting to open a case.
We need a car to tail him.
I want a new car
assigned to Section 2.
Before work tomorrow morning,
have it ready for us.
Thank you, Director.
Institutes 761 and 766
have overlapping schedules for Beijing.
Now we have the magnet.
The only thing I haven't figured out
is who to assign as his lead tail.
Who do you want to send?
Mutton hotpot, sweet garlic.
The standard set.
Cabbage, glass noodles, tofu.
And that sesame paste flatbread.
Hello.
Hello. Where are you heading?
Beijing.
Please show your IDs.
Taiwanese compatriot.
For two.
Please show the other ID.
Your ID.
Hard to tell which of us is the secretary.
I'll know the drill next time.
That'll be one thousand yuan for two.
Please check your luggage.
Put your luggage here.
Here are your tickets and IDs.
Have a pleasant journey.
Thanks.
Then take dried shrimp,
and toss them in.
Can you even call that mutton hotpot anymore?
That's how they do it in the Northeast.
Just like the rich guys.
Some wear gold bracelets.
They're just copying Hong Kongers and...
Hello.
Two tickets to Beijing.
Okay.
Here.
Have a pleasant journey.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Come, come.
Let's not meet again once we get to Beijing.
Here are some mooncakes for you.
Happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
Wishing you good health.
Chief Hao, we brought you mooncakes.
Your favorite, Yongding mooncakes.
Can your teeth still chew them?
He can't hear you.
He couldn't even chew them last year.
Happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
Wishing you good health.
Thanks. Thank you.
Here.
You need to get those teeth fixed.
Happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
Wishing you good health.
Auntie Li.
Xiao Wu.
How are your eyes doing?
Can you see the news broadcast clearly?
Keep your voice down.
I can hear you.
Auntie Li, mooncakes for you.
When Auntie Li was young,
she had the eyes of a hawk.
Anyone trying to sneak in from the other side
through the sea,
no matter how dark it was,
Auntie Li could spot them at a glance.
Right, Auntie Li?
Auntie Li, Happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
Wishing you good health.
Happy Mid-Autumn Festival.
To be honest, even today,
I still feel intimidated when I see her.
When I was young and talked to her,
I didn't even dare to look her in the eye.
She's that fierce?
We're both from Lianjiang County.
Back then,
Dinghai Bay was still called Spy Island.
Right across the sea was Matsu Island.
Those who sneaked in from Taiwan, China,
basically all landed in Lianjiang County.
Auntie Li was a militia company commander in her youth.
Once, she caught
a covert squad claiming they would
"counterattack the mainland."
There were about 30 or 40 of them.
They arrested them overnight,
capturing both the men and their weapons.
Not a single one escaped.
They even seized a small radio transmitter.
She kept it at home instead of turning it in,
claiming it was her trophy.
When I first got here, she had just retired.
I heard that
she had a terrible temper
and would scold anyone she caught.
She'd curse in her dialect.
If you provoked her,
she'd chew you out completely.
She had seniority, merits, and authority.
She was also my mentor.
A strict master trains a skilled apprentice.
Without her, you wouldn't be my mentor either.
Your skilled apprentice has set off by now, right?
Ma Qi and He Chunxiao.
How are they doing?
Trust those you use, and don't use those you doubt.
You taught me that.
From Taiwan, China, to here,
and from here to Beijing.
That's quite a big detour.
Representatives from over a dozen research institutes
are all heading to Beijing to receive awards.
Aerospace, missiles, fuels...
All the prime targets are gathered there.
If I were a demon,
I'd come down the mountain for a bite too.
All departments have deployed agents.
Every single target must be well protected.
What's your analysis on Lin Kanshan?
Who is he acting as a middleman for in Beijing this time?
It's still unclear.
Right now,
we can only suspect the thief,
but we don't know who the victim is yet.
We have no choice but to keep an eye on Lin Kanshan,
and wait for the gathered intel.
Just a Monkey King and his little sidekick...
Beijing is so big.
Can they keep an eye on the demon?
This morning, right?
Real name or anonymous?
Engineer Cao? He's right next to me.
Yes, yes. We just arrived in Beijing.
Alright, alright.
Got it.
Who was that?
What is it?
It's about your promotion to Deputy Chief Engineer.
There's a bit of a problem.
What problem?
A problem with me?
Does someone have an issue with me?
I don't have the details yet.
Don't get anxious just yet.
The organization will investigate thoroughly.
If they have an issue, they should use their real name.
Have them come to me.
I'll talk to them face to face.
Chairman Mao
It's really big.
Let me.
Give it to me.
Give me the IDs.
Have a nice day.
Thank you.
This way.
Welcome.
Hello, we have a reservation.
For two.
How many nights?
Boss, how many nights are we staying?
Two nights for now.
Do we get a discount for staying two nights in a row?
I'm sorry.
We don't offer any discounts here.
Alright, just check us in.
Hurry up.
Wait a minute.
What's that member rate about?
Are we members?
Can you keep your voice down?
How many rooms?
Two rooms.
Thank you, boss.
This hotel feels so big.
Boss, this way, this way.
My goodness.
Can you let me out, please?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Sorry, sorry.
You're in my way.
Just be more careful.
Alright, that's enough.
I'm sorry.
My goodness.
Just be more careful.
It was her suitcase blocking the way.
Alright, that's enough.
She's used to being bossy.
Help me find my slippers.
In the restroom.
Found it.
Here.
Make a pot of tea.
Okay.
Boss, there's no water in this kettle.
I'll go boil some for you.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
Come here and sit.
What for?
What do you think a secretary does?
Massage my shoulders.
Rub my lower back.
I'm tired from the long car ride.
Come here.
Just come here.
What do you think I'm trying to do?
I pay your salary,
pay for your flights and hotels.
I spend so much money.
If I wanted to be a creep, I wouldn't have picked you.
What on earth are you thinking?
Unbelievable.
What are you looking at?
Go, go, get out.
Like a block of wood.
I can't get into my room.
Just pick up the receiver to monitor.
If you want drinks, call for them yourself.
Someone will bring them up to you.
Brother Qi.
You can really hear the voices from upstairs.
Loud and clear.
You're not even on a phone call.
Covering it so God doesn't hear?
Back in basic training,
didn't Wu Jiali train you guys?
Who installed this equipment?
Look at the Beijing Bureau's gear.
Then look at ours.
Were there other comrades?
You think this is a movie?
One person tailing one car?
With so many of our comrades around,
you didn't spot a single one.
We work in three shifts.
You take the first shift.
Wake me if you hear anything interesting.
Open the door.
The bathrobes and iron are inside.
Now look over here.
The hair dryer is in that bag.
Do you know how to turn on the TV?
I do.
Call the front desk if you need anything.
We're paying for this.
Stop asking me over and over again.
By the way, boss.
I still need to ask you something.
For the next few days,
do we have any plans?
Do I need to prepare in advance?
We rest first.
Then we'll go sightseeing.
And I'll take you for hot pot, okay?
Hard to tell who the secretary is here.
Does this monitor only pick up
this female student's room?
Can we hear Lin Kanshan's room?
Is this the front desk?
I wanted to ask...
how to get to Wangfujing?
What did you hear?
Brother Qi.
How do you fall asleep and wake up just like that?
What did you hear?
He asked the front desk how to get to Wangfujing.
He seems to be heading out now.
What's our move?
It's dry in Beijing.
Drink more water.
Okay.
Let's move.
Are there any vantage points when tailing someone?
What do you mean by a vantage point?
A place where I can hide myself,
and still keep an eye on him.
Is there a specific spot like that?
If you find a sweet spot like that, let me know.
The first rule of tailing
is never treat your target like a fool.
If you think it's a good spot, so will they.
They'll look for the same spots you do.
So you have to adapt.
Be unpredictable.
Forget what the textbooks say.
Forget about any bullshit vantage points.
Look ahead. Watch the target.
Rely on yourself.
Candied hawthorns!
The simplest way
is to not let him spot you.
Memorize the layout.
Stay out of his sight as much as possible.
Take a shortcut
and wait for him on the other side.
Have you been to Beijing before?
You know this place so well.
Excuse me, buddy.
Alright, thank you.
Tanghulu!
All right, where we are right now
is the core building of the Forbidden City,
the Hall of Supreme Harmony.
This Hall of Supreme Harmony
is the largest palace in the Forbidden City.
All right, let's come over here and take a look.
Now, our Hall of Supreme Harmony
is not just the largest palace in the Forbidden City...
Come on, come on!
Hurry up!
Come over for a picture!
Three...
Two...
Excuse me, excuse me.
Cheese!
Brother Qi,
I need to use the restroom.
Is there a toilet around?
Do you know what a hand-drawn map is?
What is a hand-drawn map?
Candied hawthorn!
Sweet and crispy candied hawthorn!
How much for one?
Fifty cents a skewer.
One yuan for two.
I'll take two.
All right, take your pick.
Okay.
A map is dead, it's outdated.
A hand-drawn one is alive, in real-time.
Whether in Minzhong or Beijing,
navigating alleys or walking the main streets,
you must be familiar with every inch of the place.
At least more familiar than your opponent.
At least familiar enough that you don't need to look around
to know where the toilet is.
Where is it?
Is there one nearby?
We passed one two minutes ago.
Don't bother looking.
There's a long line of tourists at the door.
You'd wet your pants before it's your turn.
If you had a hand-drawn map,
the first thing you'd do
is mark all the public toilets
on it.
The key to tailing isn't just vantage points,
but also toilets.
A bladder is like a flour sack.
It expands the longer you hold it in.
Remember,
if you're heading out to tail someone,
drink less water from now on.
How do you know
whether this guest who's never been to Beijing
is going back to the hotel next,
or heading to the Great Wall?
But when you left,
didn't you drink hot tea too?
I didn't drink any.
I poured that for you.
You can't let a full bladder kill you.
Just pee your pants if you can't hold it.
Even a one-year-old knows that.
And you still don't get it.
Brother Qi.
What is it?
No...
We're at the hotel.
All the dishes are served.
Taipei has a Palace Museum,
and there's one here too.
But there's no comparison.
Everything is just bigger on the mainland.
The tour guide told me
that many rooms inside the Palace Museum
aren't even open to the public.
My legs are numb from all the walking,
and we haven't even seen half of it.
Think about where you want to go tomorrow.
Boss,
did you hire me just to travel with you?
There are many types of secretaries.
You're the most clueless one.
Nothing comes for free.
Do you know which business is the most profitable right now?
Military enterprises.
I'm Wang Kai,
inviting you to watch the TV drama
"Confrontation."
Who do you think he's here to make contact with?
I have a feeling
he's not here to make contact.
It's a smokescreen.
There's a coat on the bar.
The size should be a perfect fit for you.
How many tickets do you need?
One.
I'm by myself too.
How about we share a rental?